<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<suppressions xmlns="https://www.owasp.org/index.php/OWASP_Dependency_Check_Suppression">
    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
   file name: solr-*.jar
   OWASP is getting confused by our version number being on a jar with solr in the name we are on solr 6.0+ which is not affected by this issue.
   ]]></notes>
        <cve>CVE-2012-6612</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress>
        <notes><![CDATA[
        this CVE is generating a lot of false positives it should only include jackson-dataformat-xml jar
         but it is catching all jackson dependencies unfortunately I can't fix it so if we start depending
          on a vulnerable version of jackson-dataformat-xml this will sill suppress it.
   ]]></notes>
        <cve>CVE-2016-3720</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            FasterXML jackson-databind through 2.8.10 and 2.9.x through 2.9.3 allows unauthenticated remote code
            execution because of an incomplete fix for the CVE-2017-7525 deserialization flaw. This is exploitable by
            sending maliciously crafted JSON input to the readValue method of the ObjectMapper, bypassing a blacklist
            that is ineffective if the Spring libraries are available in the classpath.
            We have upgraded to 2.9.4 which fixes the issue but version 2.6.3 is still being used by
            org.apache.cxf:cxf-rt-rs-security-sso-saml -> ehcache-2.10.4 -> jackson-databind-2.6.3.
            This suppression can be removed when DDF-3593 has been completed.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2017-17485</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            FasterXML jackson-databind through 2.8.10 and 2.9.x through 2.9.3 allows unauthenticated remote code
            execution. This is exploitable by sending maliciously crafted JSON input to the readValue method of
            the ObjectMapper, bypassing a blacklist that is ineffective if the Spring libraries are available
            in the classpath. We have upgraded to 2.9.4 which fixes the issue but version 2.6.3 is still
            being used by org.apache.cxf:cxf-rt-rs-security-sso-saml/ehcache-2.10.4/jackson-databind-2.6.3.
            This suppression can be removed when DDF-3593 has been completed.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2017-7525</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress>
        <notes>
            CVE-2016-1000031: Applies to commons-fileupload-1.2.1, suppressing because the vulnerable class DiskFileItem is not used in the project
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2016-1000031</cve>
    </suppress>

    <!--
    CVE-2008-0660 is a stack based buffer overflow vulnerability related to ActiveX and
    several image uploaders. This is unrelated to presto-parser, so marking as a false positive.
-->
    <suppress>
        <cve>CVE-2008-0660</cve>
    </suppress>

    <!--
    CVE-2011-2730 is related to a vulnerability in the VMware SpringSource Spring
    Framework, where OWASP flags jars that are unrelated or have no dependency on
    Spring, so marking it as a false positive.
-->
    <suppress>
        <cve>CVE-2011-2730</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress>
        <notes>
            This CVE is related to hash collisions at the Java level. This is mitigated by newer versions of Java (8+).
            See http://openjdk.java.net/jeps/180 for more information.
            xercesImpl-2.11.0.jar
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2012-0881</cve>
    </suppress>
</suppressions>
